yo what's going on everyone it is your
boy max they're true today people today
what I have for you guys is we're gonna
be doing a product review on this
- vape it's the or the Yuki - vape
however you want to call it I'm just
gonna call it the Yuki okay but I'm
gonna be doing a review on this Yuki so
these things have been like on the
freakin rides lately they've been pretty
damn popular I've seen them a lot on
snapchat just in person on the youtubes
you know so I mean a company they - fate
they sent me over a couple of these they
sent me a blue one which is this one
that I opened up and then they also sent
me a black one that I haven't opened up
yet just thought I would do like a
little product review on these until you
guys I mean what I liked about and what
I didn't like about them but before we
get into that let's get a rip on this
cheers guys I definitely hope you're
smoking along with me damn these things
hit that's for sure I like it
alright so with the Yuki as you guys
know it kind of does look like a key fog
so that is kind of cool definitely
handheld so the thing about these low
specifically about these I've seen some
other like Yuki's or key fog dates that
the section right here it's a bit longer
so that you can actually fit your whole
gram cartridge in there this is a ground
cartridge I mean it does stick out a
little bit it's not too I mean it's
nothing too annoying or anything like
that it still fits in your pocket pretty
well I mean super discreet I really like
it so I really [\h__\h] with that
let's see another thing about these
things is that it has one two that has
four different types of voltages let's
see if I can get my camera to focus on
that so it has two point eight three
point two three point six and four point
zero I personally like to keep mine on
three-point-six because once again I
kind of feel like 4.0 and I said listen
like another product review video I did
about vapes but the highest setting
always seems to be a little bit too
harsh and the lowest setting just
doesn't produce enough smoke you know
what I mean so I really like that middle
kind of middle to high setting you know
what I mean so I'm definitely gonna keep
this 3.6 but let's get another rip
forgot to tell you guys what I'm smoking
on I'm smoking on some flow it's a nice
indica book so I mean super discreet I
mean little rips hard they kind of did
make the little slit right here a bit
larger so that it can fit ground
cartridges I would kind of have to say
that's the only deficit as far as these
things go I mean once again it's just
kind of like your standard fake guys you
know so flips up you want to know what
the flip up reminds me of it reminds me
of their freaking like flip phones you
know just like you got some [\h__\h]
attitude or some [\h__\h] just I need a fake
[Music]
but I really do best with these guys so
you want to go check them out there is
gonna be a link in the description below
do you guys smoke what kind of like the
the Yuki Bates because I have seen a lot
of you snapchat me a lot of your guys's
like you keep Apes - do you guys mess
with them do you like them
personally I do I really like these
weights I think they're cool I mean it's
kind of like a new cool stylish you know
way of a thin your own stuff like that
so I mean I've really [\h__\h] with
[Music]
all right so as far as the cons go for
this thing I mean I kind of wish that
they didn't make this outer stuff
plastic I mean if they could have made
out like metal you know or something
like that the only reason why is because
people drop their babes a lot I drop my
bait ball for buck ton
you know I've stepped on my vape in the
past you know what I mean so I
definitely feel it if I step on it or
drop this you know some I thought it is
going to break so I mean that is that is
definitely a deficit of my own is
charging live how long it takes to
charge and all that it is still pretty
standard I mean it takes maybe about 3-4
hours for this thing to be fully charged
what I've noticed at least and then I
mean from the first time I've charged
this I I mean it hasn't run out of juice
on me and I've been going for about four
days I would say using this thing
consecutively so I mean hasn't ran a
juice on me been using it for four days
straight because I wanted to see how
long I could use it I wanted to see how
long I could use it you know before I
ran out of run out of battery so I could
let you guys know but it hasn't run out
of [\h__\h] battery is so the battery
life on this thing is a really long last
day you know so that's what so let's get
another rip I mean all that comes in
here it's just chorus comes with a
manual the battery charging cable and
then it comes just like with a little
bag too
that's what's up I mean do you keep vape
really don't know what else to say about
this thing just uh you know just uh just
another fake it's just another cool
looking vape another thing you do have
the if you want to use it you do have to
hit it from the side you have to keep
pressing and do I need to use it and
then oh now you run out a battery [\h__\h]
alright but anyway you gotta press it if
you want to use it I mean of course this
is just this button here's you can flip
it up and down and all that so yeah I
mean I really don't know what else to
say about this vape I mean I like it I
[\h__\h] with it it works well once again if
they could just kind of substitute the
plastic for something a little bit more
sturdier it's sturdier there we go Wow
it's sturdier then I mean it would just
it would just improve it all because
people people drop in accidentally break
their [\h__\h] you know what I mean so I'm
gonna get on out of here thank you guys
so much for tuning and I appreciate that
[\h__\h] make sure to go check out the site
you know with the bees on there get it
but thank you guys so much for tuning in
I appreciate that [\h__\h] stay in the
clouds guys
[Music]